the ORIon
You're kidding me.
Kanuma got absolutely destroyed.
He was totally toyed with.
Do you know who that guy is?
Nope.
That means he's also a first-year.
Bofurin really is bad news.
Man, Suo.
You're tough!
Oh no, not at all.
Suo-san! Was that kung fu!?
Or something like aikido!?
I'm not really sure.
My master learned on his own, too.
He said it was a hodgepodge.
I-Is that so?
M-Master?
Anyway... You get emotional too, huh?
That was unexpected.
Oh, how embarrassing.
I normally don't act like that.
But Sakura-kun definitely affected me.
Don't blame others.
But when you fight me,
you better go all out.
There you go again.
Sakura-san, that's all you talk about.
What? Sakura-kun, you seem like a nuisance
so I wouldn't want to go against you.
What do you mean, a nuisance?
A nuisance?
Calm down, Sakura-san!
Outta the way!
Looks like they're influencing
each other already.
External stimulation is really important!
I won't forget that you said
I was stupid earlier!
What? You're so petty!
- Damn you!
- Sakura-san, please calm down!
Looks like they'll make one fine team.
Ow...
Kanuma.
They got you too?
...end.
It's the end.
The end.
We're done for.
I'm jealous.
Hey, I wanna go against the eyepatch—
Okay, next.
Who'll go up next?
It's finally my turn.
Sorry, Sakura. I'm going before you.
Hey, hold on a sec!
Two first-years already went,
so why am I saved for later?
S-Sakura-san.
You're up against Togame, right?
Looks like he doesn't want to step up quite yet.
Togame is their second-in-command.
Normally, it would be proper if I face him.
Are you saying I can't win!?
That's not what I mean.
I'm trusting you.
It's not like you need to trust me.
I'll do it! And I'll win!
Anyway, what's up
with Almond Eyes over there?
He butted right in!
Do those two know each other?
Well, it seems that way.
Hiragi...
doesn't talk about himself often.
Well, him knowing someone outside
of Furin isn't anything unusual.
Sakocchan! Go for it!
Sako.
I didn't think you'd voluntarily
request a one-on-one.
Did something happen...
between you and Hiragi?
As usual, I can't tell what he's thinking.
But, but...
To watch a one-on-one between one of
Bofurin's Four Kings against Sakocchan.
This is gonna be really fun to watch.
It's been a while, Sako.
You've grown a bit taller.
So you joined Shishitoren.
I can't do anything
about how things turned out.
I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna win this one.
Hey! Screw the chitchat!
Come on, start! Start it up!
"I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna win this one"?
Even now, you still look down on me.
Disgusting.
My old self is long gone!
I'll pound that into your body!
He st...
- Good going, Sako!
- Get 'im!
H-Hiragi-san is being pressured.
No way.
Good going! Keep at it, Sakocchan!
Well... Sako is putting up...
a pretty good fight...
Of course. He's one of our top five.
Sakocchan won't be inferior,
even against Ragi-chan.
Well, I don't know
what he's thinking about...
but he's been in more fights than anyone.
When he first joined,
it felt like out of desperation.
Anyway, I didn't know Sakocchan
could talk that much.
He usually only says "yes" or "no,"
and one more word if we're lucky.
Right.
That just proves his reservations
about Hiragi, doesn't it?
Straightforward.
Your heavy reliance on pure strength.
Stupidly serious.
Nothing interesting about it at all.
You really haven't improved at all.
Meanwhile, you've gotten quite talkative.
I didn't need to teach you that you'll bite
your tongue if you chitchat during a fight.
That's how quiet you were.
What? He got even faster...
Not just lacking improvement.
You've gotten weaker.
It's because you hang out with guys like that.
Of course this would happen.
A chummy group of pushovers.
Hey.
Huh?
Not you!
Shark teeth! I'm talkin' to ya!
Ya hear me!?
Because of you, he's mocking us too!
The only weak part about you
should be your gut!
Come on, Sakura-san!
Why are you laughing, Suo-san?
Damn you!
Stop lying there doin' nothin!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Damn it, ya listenin'!?
Sakura-kun, you're starting
to care more about your friends, huh?
I was just pissed off
because he's makin' fun of us.
Yup, yup. You're right.
Come now, calm down, Sakura.
Sako, was it?
Hiragi is currently
one of the Four Kings of Bofurin.
Among which, he's leading the team
named after Tamonten.
TAMON TEAM
KOMOKU TEAM / JIKOKU TEAM
ZOJO TEAM
Do you know Tamonten's other name?
Huh?
Man, it's been a while
since I got kicked that good.
That hit hard.
But still, I showed a pathetic side.
You got crazy tough.
You're a totally different guy now.
Tamonten is also known
as Bishamonten, the god of war
who controls the battlefield.
Thanks to you, a first-year
yelled at me. How embarrassing.
All the medicine in the world won't help me.
But it's getting fun now.
Hey, don't get so cocky
just cuz you're smart.
Stop being cheeky.
Um, I didn't do anything.
I'm not being cocky.
That's what pisses us off!
You're such a weakling!
Don't show off, wimp!
What the hell are you guys doin'?
Come on, man.
It's not often that
we get to see one-on-ones like this.
So amazing.
What's with him?
He was actually that strong?
Of course. The title of Four Kings of Bofurin
is not just for decoration.
He's really famous in our town for being strong.
What? I-If he's that strong,
he shoulda gone at it from the get-go.
That said, he may have been
strong to begin with,
but I think your words
of inspiration worked well.
Good, good! Sakocchan is strong!
Right.
But this fight...
Hiragi has the upper hand.
Damn it.
There's no way your current self
is stronger than me.
I mean, think about it.
You hang out with that crowd
and live a cushy life.
So why...
Wh-Why?
"Why"?
Cuz it's bullying
no matter how you look at it.
Should I not have stopped them?
You know, if you stay quiet against
this type, it'll get to their heads.
Ya gotta fight back at least a little bit.
Can you stand up?
Teach me how to fight!
S-Sure.
Back then, you were tremendously strong.
Even though you never created
a herd of your own,
people naturally gravitated toward you.
Especially with how we met,
I had a strong admiration.
I was genuinely proud
that I could walk behind this guy.
Hiragi-san.
Congratulations on graduating.
You're finally starting at Furin.
Yeah.
Hiragi-san, I'm sure you can take
the top spot.
Someone like you
should stand above everyone else.
Hiragi-san, I'll do anything
for you to be at the top!
Please let me help you in Furin next year.
Back then, Furin wasn't unified yet.
And you would take the top spot.
I seriously thought
I would watch it happen up close.
Hey, Sako.
It's best if you didn't follow me.
What'd he say?
I decided to support this guy
named Umemiya over at Furin.
So I won't take the top spot.
Even if you follow me, there's no way
things will end up the way you're expecting.
You need to find a new goal on your own.
Why?
Wow, you did all this? You're strong.
If you'd like, why don't you join our team?
Come on, fight me, too!
You got strong guys?
But of course.
I'm strong, too!
Our philosophy is devotion to power...
The strong are recognized.
The stronger you are, the higher you'll go.
I don't care about that.
All I care about
is being able to fight strong guys.
I'll become stronger, defeat him,
and make him regret it.
There's no way I can lose!
Unlike you, I didn't get chummy with anyone.
I devoted myself to getting stronger.
From below!
There's no way I'd lose.
You decided to fall under someone else.
There's no way I'd lose!
Sako.
I'm sorry I couldn't meet your expectations.
That's not...
I'm sorry.
That's not it.
There's nothing that you need
to apologize for.
I decided to support this guy
named Umemiya over at Furin.
So I won't take the top spot.
Even if you follow me, there's no way
things will end up the way you're expecting.
I knew all along that
you were looking out for me. But...
It's best if you didn't follow me.
That was the one thing
I didn't want you to tell me.
You need to find a new goal on your own.
I know that I'm being selfish.
But still, you had always been
who I aspired to become.
I didn't care where you were,
and who you were supporting.
I simply...
wanted you to say, "Follow me."
Hiragi-san.
I'll follow you forever, Hiragi-san.
What's this all of a sudden?
I already made up my mind.
Hiragi-san, you're a guy
who will take the top spot.
When you're taking the top spot,
and even after that, I will always follow you.
That's what I decided.
H-Hey.
No way.
S-Sako lost.
So that's one of Bofurin's Four Kings,
Toma Hiragi.
Well, that was an amazing fight.
Oh man.
Sakocchan lost.
I guess Ragi-chan is really powerful!
I wanna go against him!
I don't care who.
Can someone get him off the stage?
It's fine.
I'll do it myself.
Gee, thank you, thank you.
You didn't have to handle him so gently.
Okay, thanks for everything.
What?
Can't you wait until after
your one-on-one to deal with him?
I mean, you don't know
what's gonna happen.
What do you mean by that?
Who knows...
Well, this is me talking to myself,
but I don't think doing stuff like this
will make your team stronger.
That's quite a bit of talkin' to yourself.
You can do it when you try.
G-Great work up there!
Great job.
I can't possibly
ask anything about the opponent.
Well done.
Yeah.
Your roundhouse kick is fierce as always.
I never wanna get hit with that.
You're not gonna ask?
Ask what?
Like who that guy is,
or what happened between us.
You wanna talk about that?
Uh, well, that's not what I meant.
Then I don't wanna hear it.
When you wanna talk, tell me.
That's the story I wanna hear.
Gotcha.
VOW TO FOLLOW
Shishitoren's baseball jackets.
They look like uniforms,
and it really gives that team feel.
That's not my style.
No way!
Baseball jackets are pretty cool!
The origins of those jackets came from souvenir jackets
for the military folks stationed in Yokosuka!
That's why the designs often have
an East Asian feel, like dragons and tigers!
Looks like I triggered
something in this guy's head.